<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Doxti.Tech</title>
    <link>https://doxti.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Doxti.Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 07:13:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://doxti.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>End of February 2019 Update </title>
      <link>https://doxti.tech/posts/end-of-february-2019-update-.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 07:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doxti.tech/posts/end-of-february-2019-update-.html</guid>
      <description>We have an update to https://doxti.com ! First, we have a mascot! And did a few changes that can be very important to some, we know they are to us. Here are most of the changes. (any remaining changes are specific to functionality, very technical and just a few)
Ui Changes  new home screen that&amp;rsquo;s 3 parts  Home page Login page New Register page  We added a privacy policy and a cookie policy page linking from the register page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019 Update / patch 1.1</title>
      <link>https://doxti.tech/posts/february-2019-update-_-patch-1_1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 05:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doxti.tech/posts/february-2019-update-_-patch-1_1.html</guid>
      <description>Quick Download bug fix In case you noticed, the download functionality was off since the last update. A bug from outer space was the culprit in this case.(the . from the zip file was not being set when generating the file, and the zip file was corrupt as a result. I promised a logo on next update, but this was more of a patch, with one major fix. so no logo yet, but download works!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2019 update 1</title>
      <link>https://doxti.tech/posts/february-2019-update-1.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doxti.tech/posts/february-2019-update-1.html</guid>
      <description>For the month of February 2019, even though multiple updates and releases are planned, this is the first one:
Functionality Changes:  Repository is now saved and automatically selected from the dropdown after you published once with a selected repository. So you don&amp;rsquo;t have to search for your repository where you want to publish a certain site, the repository is saved once selected and published once, and this happens for each site individually moved Github App to doxtitech username new dropdown in configuration page to select and change default theme (Still just 1 theme) now when you download a site you get a website-title.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>28-29 Jan 2019 Update</title>
      <link>https://doxti.tech/posts/29-jan-2019-update.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 19:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doxti.tech/posts/29-jan-2019-update.html</guid>
      <description>What changed?  All file names that are created new now have _ where special characters should be, but the title remains the same You have now the ability to select more repositories to publish to. Previously you had the ability to select the first 30, now it&amp;rsquo;s the first 100. More will follow later (We&amp;rsquo;re thinking infinite) *A losing bug was fixed for losing repositories, that was not loading the list of repositories properly before  That&amp;rsquo;s it for today, not much, but important for our users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>27 Jan 2019 Update</title>
      <link>https://doxti.tech/posts/27-jan-2019-update.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doxti.tech/posts/27-jan-2019-update.html</guid>
      <description>As part of the End of January Update for Doxti.com, there where a few changes made for this update to our service, to provide a better experience for our current and future users. Here is a list of changes, explained
Aesthetic Changes  Removed datepicker from login forn - all we wanted is to make sure that the people registering are not underage for the internet Red Warning text on download page, not so scary anymore - we listened to feedback and the text on the download page was scary, because it was red and big enough to intimidate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post!</title>
      <link>https://doxti.tech/posts/first-post.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doxti.tech/posts/first-post.html</guid>
      <description>But not just any post This post was created using https://doxti.com and is the first post for the tech blogging of doxti.tech. Of course, this first post is not going to be techie. But it is going to say something.
Doxti SRL is a small fresh company from Cluj Napoca. It&amp;rsquo;s main product right now, is https://doxti.com, which is a static site generator User interface. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s a Admin Panel for HUGO from http://gohugo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>